#### Contact

+97686893669 (Mobile) contact@dorjnyam.com

www.linkedin.com/in/dorjnyam (LinkedIn)

www.youracclaim.com/users/ dorjnyamt/badges (Personal) dorjnyam.com (Blog)

### Top Skills

Deep Learning
Python (Programming Language)
Technology Trends

#### Languages

Mongolian (Native or Bilingual) English (Professional Working) Japanese (Limited Working) Korean (Elementary)

#### Certifications

Certified Information Technology Professional FE

Apache Cassandra 3 Developer Associate Certification

Al Programming with Python

Honors-Awards
ITPEC Award - 31st ITPEC FE

#### **Publications**

Emergency Detection for Personalized U-healthcare System

# Dorjnyam Tumur-Ochir

Senior R&D Engineer at ICT GROUP

Ulaanbaatar, Mongolia

## Summary

I have double majored in Computer Science and Business & Technology Management at Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology. I employ my expertise in both fields to provide value to projects and systems based on information technology.

I have been working as bid specialist on tenders from international organizations like ADB, GIZ, UNDP, WBG, IFC and national government organizations and have won multiple bids from these organizations.

I am currently pursuing following certifications: CAPM of PMI, ECBA of IIBA, CCNA of Cisco, CISSP and SSCP of ISC(2), and ITPEC FE.

## Experience

ICT GROUP MONGOLIA

3 years 7 months

Senior Research And Development Engineer March 2022 - Present (1 year 8 months)

Ulaanbaatar, Mongolia

Research And Development Engineer September 2021 - February 2022 (6 months)

Ulaanbaatar, Mongolia

**Business Analyst** 

April 2020 - September 2021 (1 year 6 months)

Ulaanbaatar, Mongolia

## Education

Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology

Bachelor of Science - BS, Business and Technology Management and Computer Science · (March 2015 - February 2022)

Korea Science Academy of KAIST High School Diploma · (March 2012 - February 2015)